<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Estate Training by Tiffany Fykes</title>
    <description>Tiffany Fykes, a top Real Estate Agent in Nashville, shares her own internal real estate agent training for free. Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>realestatecareersintn.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="realestatecareersintn.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:36:47 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:36:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tiffany Fykes's Journey Through Real Estate</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lR2KriVxmHo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out this interview to learn about Tiffany Fyke’s journey through real estate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 15:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>realestatecareersintn.com/tiffany-fykess-journey-through-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">realestatecareersintn.com/tiffany-fykess-journey-through-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Which Neighborhood Should You Farm?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jij0h9Fdp3w?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running a real estate business involves a lot of community building and marketing to a specific neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realtors call this “farming,” and I recently got a great question on this very subject. Mary in Houston asks, &lt;strong&gt;“How should agents choose a neighborhood to farm?”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two main questions agents should consider when picking a neighborhood to farm:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Does the neighborhood have a good turnover rate?&lt;/strong&gt; An ideal neighborhood for farming would be one where people actually move semi-frequently. Therefore, aim for neighborhoods with a turnover rate of at least 6%. The bigger the turnover rate a neighborhood has, the better. To determine an area’s turnover rate, compare the number of recent sales versus the total number of homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The bigger the turnover rate a neighborhood has, the better.%20realestatecareersintn.com/which-neighborhood-should-you-farm.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The bigger the turnover rate a neighborhood has, the better.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Is there already a dominant real estate agent in the neighborhood?&lt;/strong&gt; When considering this point, remember that any agent who has 15% of the market share for a given neighborhood is considered dominant. Also, if two agents combined have 20% of a neighborhood’s market share, they would be considered dominant, as well. Though it is possible to farm a neighborhood that already has a dominant agent, I personally wouldn’t recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 10:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>realestatecareersintn.com/which-neighborhood-should-you-farm.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">realestatecareersintn.com/which-neighborhood-should-you-farm.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
